Okay.
I'm sorry, who's in the bottom right hand side here
that just came on?
Why don't we go ahead and raise your hand? So I'm Bill
and
William.
That's William, and we all know our, we got Jerry and I'm Jerry. Jerry,
and in the middle here,
I'm sorry, with the glasses and the mustache.
Gary Partridge.
I'm sorry?
Gary Partridge. Oh, Gary Partridge.
Okay, great. You are Or you're talking Jim.
So, all right. So that's why I didn't recognize you because applicants.
Okay, very good. So, don't we go ahead and
get started. I don't know if Walter's gonna join us later or not. Okay, so we'll call to meeting to order. It's 07:03
according to my clock. Is that good for everybody?
Good for me. Good for me. Okay. So, we don't have any alternates because we have a full
house, if you will. So, we don't need any alternates, right?
And
I don't know if anybody has any additions or changes to the agenda, but we just have the one
application before us tonight.
Is that correct, Jim? Yes, it is.
Okay,
so the application we have in front of us tonight is
from Gary and Elizabeth Partridge
and
they're at 151 Lakeside Drive and they're basically
seeking
relief from section 11.2,
town of Ann Arbor zoning regulations,
calls for a 50 foot setback. Actually, this one says 50 foot to zero,
but then I thought I saw it from 25 foot to five foot.
Maybe you can clarify that, Gary.
>> In section eleven two
they give you 50
feet is the cumulative
setback.
>> Oh the cumulative I got you. So it's
two sides. Jim the way I way I read this is that
the property itself isn't
is a non conforming lot to start with because
it was put in way before our current
guidelines
>> or regulations.
So,
I guess my first question would be is, has there been any
communication from either the other two property owners on either side,
either 157
or the other one was a Vernon
address.
I don't
That other address is 4 Sunset Lane? Yes.
>> The owner happens to be in Vernon. In Vernon. So do we know they aware of the application and have they made any comments or anything like that?
Aware of the application.
They're aware of the application?
>> Yeah because we serve them the letters that Jim gave us.
Okay.
>> And deliver and I've had to sign out there
for the appropriate amount of time. Yeah. Maybe all
this.
>> And Jim, do you know if we've had any
I have not received any comments, no. Any comments at all? Okay, fantastic. I'm sorry, who just joined us at the
This is
John Mendez. We're at 157
Lakeside.
>> Okay, on the property adjoining 157. Well,
thank you for joining us. So I was just asking if we had any comments or
feedback from the neighbors on either side. So do you have any objections or comments concerning this application? We have no objections at all concerning the application.
Okay,
thank you very much.
Have we heard anything Jim? Do you know from anybody from the applicant on 4 Sunset Lane? I have not. We have not.
Do
any other members on the board have any questions or comments concerning
the application?
No, I don't.
No.
None by me.
>> Jerry and okay.
Do I So Jim, do I go to a motion to accept the application then if there's no other comments or discussion?
Are you saying a motion to approve?
Yes.
Motion to approve, yes. Do that, certainly.
>> So do I have a motion to approve the application as it is written?
>> I will move to approve the application as it is written.
>> Mindy, you know who that is?
You do. Fantastic.
Okay. Would anybody like to second the motion as
it is written?
I'll second the motion as it is written.
>> That's William.
Fantastic.
Okay. So then is there any further discussion?
Can we have a roll call? All in favor,
if you could just raise your hand in favor.
Aye. And
for Kathleen, good, thank you very much. It doesn't look there's any opposed here. So, I believe that means
you have got your application.
>> Well,
thank you very much to the commission and also thanks, thanks to our very good neighbors, John and Jan. I appreciate their support. Very kind of you to join us tonight. And
>> so very good. Is there anything else they need to do, Jim,
going forward from here or is it all set?
>> They will have to file a variance, a notice on the land records.
>> Okay. And you're all, are you all set with that,
Gary?
I don't understand what he just said.
>> There's there's a notice that needs to be filed on the land records.
You provide that
for me? I provide that. Yes. Okay. There's a
notice that goes in the paper, but it's of action.
There's an appeal period
that starts
clock on
that notice.
I believe it's fifteen days.
Nobody wants to appeal it. They have to do it within that time period. I also prepare a notice. The notice basically just mirrors
what is in the legal notice.
Is it this applicant? I mean, it's a property right.
That's why it goes in the land. I mean, if you sell the property tomorrow,
variance
is in place. That's what that's all about.
Will provide that notice.
There's a filing fee of maybe $20
and then you fill a building permit.
You just go through the building permit process at that time.
>> Okay, okay. We will do our next step with the building permit. Thank you very much. Okay. Thank you guys. You're obviously welcome to stay on. I don't really think there's anything else, but you're welcome to stay on or leave whenever
you're ready.
Is there any other
open discussion or anything else to be brought before the board tonight?
I'll take that as a no. We also have our minutes that we need to approve from
September.
Does anybody have any comments? Has everybody had a chance to read the minutes? And does anybody have any comments or corrections
for the minutes?
I've read them. Look to be in good order.
I'll just note that we are still looking for
one alternate and if anybody out there knows of someone that would like to become an alternate on the zoning board of appeals,
please forward their name to me. That'd be fantastic.
But other than that,
the only other action we really had was to
try and come up with a
what do you call it? An assistant vice chair
or vice chair.
And I know we had some people we asked last time, they wanted more time. I don't know if anybody's
interested in raising their hand at this time or if we'd like to just continue
as we are.
So, I'll just open that up. Has anybody changed their mind about becoming a vice chair?
Basically a vice chair does what I'm doing right now.
You just leave the meeting
and you can see how hard that is to do.
So,
okay. I'll take that as a no for now.
>> As a comment. Yes.
Lacking a vice chair, the committee would simply nominate one of its members
that are at
a meeting to lead a meeting of the specific meeting.
>> Okay, so we asked our members last time and at that time
basically no one was interested in becoming the vice chair and we basically said
that
a few people would just want to kind of see how things happen and what the responsibilities were
and Lacking
a vice chair, it's simply
>> a chair is picked. In your absence, a chair is picked for a Oh, at the next meeting. Okay, very good. People understand what the process is.
>> Very good. Do
we need to listen to your administrative report from our zoning agent,
>> Jim? I really have nothing. I may have reported I am currently working on amendments to the lake
lake regulations,
which which are are intended to
improve the quality the water quality of the lake.
They're Gotcha. They're fairly expensive.
They're they're they're intended to cut down the phosphorus and
or the phosphate nitrogen
loading of the lake.
And there's complicated formulas, and there may be a bigger role for the ZBA
at such time as those regulations are
are adopted.
I
will get them out when they're probably finalized,
I can get them out, people want to take a look at them now,
they're in a draft form,
and they're gonna, quite frankly,
it's going to cost people some money to comply with.
So there may be some issues.
But I think you will see more applications
variances at such time as those regulations are adopted.
Gotcha.
>> Okay.
All right.
Well, I guess for now we are good. So as far as the meetings from September 2, do
we have a motion to approve the meetings as the notes as written?
>> I'll move that we approve the meeting minutes for 09/02/2020.
>> Thank you. And do we have a second for that? I second that Kathleen Storka. Thank
you, Kathleen. All those in favor say yay. Yea.
All those opposed?
Fantastic.
Well,
unless there's anything else anybody wants to discuss,
I'd entertain a motion to adjourn.
>> Bill, before we adjourn,
you got my email that I had sent to
Carol Lee
resigning as an alternate
and requesting to be placed as a regular member on the ZBA.
I
>> did get that. Yes. And do I have to do anything else now besides that?
>> I don't think so because you were already sworn in. Is that correct?
>> I was sworn in as an alternate. And Jim, he doesn't have to be re sworn in, does he? I think he would. He would have to. I would double check with Carol. Yeah, resigned.
>> Yeah, absolutely. Yeah. Okay. So you are, so you'd to go and see Carol and get sworn in again then? Yeah. All right. I just want to make sure that everybody was in agreement to have me as a full member.
>> Oh, we are all just so happy to have you. Oh, thank you. We are thrilled.
>> Just so
the commission knows, there is
Carol Lee does periodically advertise any vacancies in the River East. And there is a
is a page on the website for volunteer opportunities.
But other than that,
if anybody's
guest,
anybody knows of an individual who might want to serve,
step forward.
>> Yeah, let us know. Okay, great. Alright, so if you get a chance before our next meeting, that'd be great if you get in and go and see Carol Lee or I'll give her a call. Perfect, very good. Thank you.
Have a question. So
>> in the beginning,
we didn't see any alternates. Would we need to, if he's not a full member, would we need to have sat him as an alternate?
>> Well, was voted in as a full member. It's just that he didn't get sworn in yet. I
think Jim is that okay that he's in as a a full member right now? Sure as I know, yeah. Yeah, I don't think it's an issue. Think we're all set Mindy. Thank you for calling. Okay,
so I'm gonna go back to my last thing. Do we have a motion from anybody on the floor to adjourn?
I think we did, right? Yes. I think we did that. Kathleen, do we have a second?
I second it if we need one. Well, I think you've made the motion, right? Or was that I second it. Okay.
Then all those in favor,
raise your hand and say aye.
Aye.
>> Aye. Right. Thank you everybody
for coming tonight and welcome Mindy. Thank you for being here tonight.
And we'll talk next time we have a application before us. Great. Thanks for your help, Bill. Thanks very much. Take care, You're
>> in a quick meeting, Bill.
I like it. Pretty quick.
Fifteen minutes.
>> Oh. Unlike the board of ed That's my promise go down for eighteen. Yeah. He should be the chair of the board of ed. Get those over. Love
>> it. Alright, guys. Take care. Thank you. Thanks very much. Good night. Good night.